Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
- NFIAC (National Federation of Insurance Agents Council), Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Coal Cracker, 1953; Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.1:no.12
  - Item 3: correspondence, 1949; Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Financial report for the month of may, 1951, Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Grievance procedures, Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
    Author: International Union of Life Insurance Agents
  - Item 6: miscellaneous flyers and correspondence, Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: News and Views, 1951; Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
    Author: Mar-Tol-Del-VA. & D.C.
  - Item 8: Our Voice, 1949; Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.11:no.2,3
  - Item 9: Press release, 1951; Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Queen City Local RU ready?, 1951; Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Thoughts on a legislative program, 1951; Publication (Box 217, Folder 4)
    Author: Jack Bradon
- NFIAC (National Federation of Insurance Agents Council), Publication (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: NFIAC Reporter, 1950; Publication (Box 217, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.1:no.3-12
  - Item 2: NFIAC Reporter, 1951; Publication (Box 217, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-6, 8-12
  - Item 3: NFIAC Reporter, 1952; Publication (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Our Voice, 1949; Publication (Box 217, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.11:no.6
  - Item 5: Our Voice, 1949-1950 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.12, no.11-12
  - Item 6: Our Voice, 1950; Publication (Box 217, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.13:no.6,8-9
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents., Publication (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Code of ethics, Publication (Box 218, Folder 1)
    Author: Insurance Agents International Union. Local 19 (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 2: District Chairman's basic manual, Publication (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Grievance procedures, Publication (Box 218, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union of Life Insurance Agents. Local 19 (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 4: News Digest, 1953; Publication (Box 218, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.3:no.11-13, 18, 20-21
  - Item 5: News Digest, 1957; Publication (Box 218, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.7:no.1-2
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents., Publication (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: News Digest, 1955; Publication (Box 218, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents., Publication (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Press releases, Publication (Box 218, Folder 3)
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents., Publication (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agents seek wage boost, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Insurance agents of Prudential Co. plan strike vote, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Insurance agents reject contract, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Insurance agents seek higher pay, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Insurance firm, agents sign pact, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Prudential agent union in agreement, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Prudential agents ask higher pay, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Prudential, Union to talk contract, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Union is ending Prudential pact, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Union ratifies two-year pact, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Insurance unit takes strike vote, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Our voice, a ray of hope, 1953-1954 (Box 218, Folder 4)
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents., Publication (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Death of a salesman, 1952; Publication (Box 218, Folder 5)
    Author: New York Post
  - Item 2: Forum, 1951; Publication (Box 218, Folder 5)
    Author: International Union of Life Insurance Agents.
    Notes: vol.2:no.7-9, 11
  - Item 3: miscellaneous minutes and correspondence, 1951; Publication (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: New England Speaks, 1953; Publication (Box 218, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.1:no.7-8
  - Item 5: Prudential Insurance strike mapped, 1951; Publication (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Scope, 1950; Publication (Box 218, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.3:no.8
  - Item 7: Scope, 1951; Publication (Box 218, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.4:no.6-9
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents., Publication (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: correspondence, Publication (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Manual for handling grievances, Publication (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Briefcase, Publication (Box 218, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.2
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents., Publication (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Insurance Agent, 1953; Publication (Box 218, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.3:no.2-8, 10-12
  - Item 2: The Insurance Agent, 1953; Publication (Box 218, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1, 4-7, 9-10
- International Union of Life Insurance Agents., Publication (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The key tojob security, higher pay, improved working conditions, Publication (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Double security for you, Publication (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Prudential negotiations, Publication (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The future is easy to face when you are all together, Publication (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Your best, Publication (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Security, security, security for insurance agents, Publication (Box 218, Folder 8)
- IWA (Insurance Workers of America), Publication (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: CIO Insurance News Letter, 1951; Publication (Box 219, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1:no.17- 20
  - Item 2: CIO Insurance News Letter, 1952; Publication (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Metropolitan Grievance Committee Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The CIO News (Insurance Edition), 1952; Publication (Box 219, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.2:no.2- 3
  - Item 5: The CIO News (Insurance Edition), 1953; Publication (Box 219, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.3:no.4, 6- 7
- IWA (Insurance Workers of America), Publication (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Debit Reporter, 1954; Publication (Box 219, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-2. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Debit Reporter, 1955; Publication (Box 219, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.2:no.2. 2 copies
  - Item 3: Insurance is our business, too!, 1951; Publication (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Seventeen Fifteen News - Arrived, 1958; Publication (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The CIO Debit, 1954; Publication (Box 219, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.1:no.27-28
  - Item 6: The Debit, 1956; Publication (Box 219, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1956 January
- IWA (Insurance Workers of America), Publication (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The New York Debit, 1957; Publication (Box 219, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.2, no.1 (1957)
  - Item 2: The New York Debit, 1959; Publication (Box 219, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 3, no.4 (1959)
  - Item 3: The New York Debit, 1960; Publication (Box 219, Folder 3)
    Notes: 1960 (Jan., Apr)
  - Item 4: The New York Debit, 1961; Publication (Box 219, Folder 3)
    Notes: 1961 (Jan., Nov.)
- IWA (Insurance Workers of America), Publication (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Danger! Money out of your pockets, Publication (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Did you know?, Publication (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The insurance you lack, Publication (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Insurance Workers International Union AFL-CIO, Executive Board Meeting, 1960; Publication (Box 219, Folder 4)
    Notes: Report
  - Item 5: IWA Membership can meanto you, Publication (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: When buying your insurance look for the union label, Publication (Box 219, Folder 4)
- IWA (Insurance Workers of America), Publication (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: It is in your interest, Publication (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: New Quaker City pact wins security rights, Publication (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Successful grievance procedure: a manual for IWA-CIO Office Grievance Committeemen, Publication (Box 219, Folder 5)
    Author: Insurance Workers of America
  - Item 4: Union Affairs, 1959; Publication (Box 219, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.1:no.14 (1959)
  - Item 5: What you should know about the MIC, Publication (Box 219, Folder 5)
- IWA (Insurance Workers of America), Publication (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: roster of Local 5 Executive Board (1965), Publication (Box 219, Folder 6)
- Insurance Agents International Union, Publication (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Local 19, Insurance Agents' International Union, having among its aims the unity and brotherhood of Insurance Agents, 1956; Publication (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Union Affairs, 1959; Publication (Box 219, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.1:no.8
- Insurance Agents International Union, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Agents Security Check-Up, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Cold facts, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Line Management, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Organization your road to New Frontiers on your job, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: That message from the boss, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: The key to, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Then and now, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Why join a union?, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Fought any dragons lately?, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Wishing won't work, Publication (Box 219, Folder 8)
- Insurance Workers International Union, Publication (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Insurance Workers International Union, 1962; Publication (Box 219, Folder 9)
    Notes: Structure chart.
- Insurance Workers International Union, Publication (Box 219, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Agreements, 1969; Publication (Box 219, Folder 10)
    Author: Insurance Workers International Union
  - Item 2: By-laws, 1968; Publication (Box 219, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Report to General Executive Board, 1968; Publication (Box 219, Folder 10)
- International Joint Conference Council, Publication (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Activities, 1920; Publication (Box 220, Folder 1)
    Author: International Joint Conference Council
  - Item 2: Digest of Minutes St. Louis., 1920; Publication (Box 220, Folder 1)
- International Labor Defense, Publication (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Reports and proceedings of the eighth convention, Publication (Box 220, Folder 2)
    Author: International Labor Defense
  - Item 2: Sedition!, Publication (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Smash the frame-up against the Anthracite Miners, Free Bonita, Mendola and Moleski!, Publication (Box 220, Folder 2)
    Author: B. K. Gebert
  - Item 4: Story of the Imperial valley, Publication (Box 220, Folder 2)
    Author: Frank Spector
  - Item 5: The tale of a rat, Publication (Box 220, Folder 2)
    Author: Bert Lorton
  - Item 6: The Ziegler Frame-Up, 1926; Publication (Box 220, Folder 2)
    Author: Max Shachtman
  - Item 7: We accuse!, 1938; Publication (Box 220, Folder 2)
    Author: Vito Marcantonio
- Gastonia, Publication (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Gastonia - a class case and a class verdict - very brittle, 1929; Publication (Box 220, Folder 3)
- ILPA (International Labor Press Association), Publication (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 1974 contest award winners, Publication (Box 220, Folder 4)
    Author: International Labor Press Association
  - Item 2: A Question of relevancy, 1971; Publication (Box 220, Folder 4)
    Author: Richard L. Harwood
  - Item 3: correspondence and flyers, 1970-1973 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: ILPA Reporter, 1976; Publication (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Journalistic Awards Contest, Judges Report, 1972; Publication (Box 220, Folder 4)
- ILPA (International Labor Press Association), Publication (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: correspondence and flyers, 1974-1978 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Journalistic Awards Contest, Judges Report, 1976-1977 (Box 220, Folder 5)
- ILPA (International Labor Press Association), Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Local publications guide, 1962; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Coordinated bargaining....what?...why?, 1962; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: ILPA press relations guide, 1965; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Postage can kill you union paper (and many others too), 1972; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Reaching them, 1971; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Speaking of labor unions; a reference manual of terms and titles in the American labor union movement, 1964; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Tell it like/as it is, 1971; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
    Author: Roy H. Copperud
  - Item 8: The alienated: the young rebels today and why they're different, 1967; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
    Author: Bayard Rustin
  - Item 9: The improper study of public opinion, 1964; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
    Author: Samuel Lubell
  - Item 10: Whose press is it?, 1965; Publication (Box 220, Folder 6)
    Author: Ben H. Bagdikian
- ILPA (International Labor Press Association), Publication (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 37th-44th year, 1948-1956 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    Author: International Labor Press of America
  - Item 2: Annual report of Executive Council, 1952; Publication (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: correspondence, 1974; Publication (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: ILPA Reporter, 1956-1961 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Labor, 1950; Publication (Box 220, Folder 7)
    Notes: Articles
  - Item 6: Labor Press Directory, 1959; Publication (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Proceedings 35th annual convention, 1946; Publication (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: The American Labor Press, Publication (Box 220, Folder 7)
    Author: Lewis M. Hermmann
  - Item 9: Way to shown to crush bogus labor papers., 1957; Publication (Box 220, Folder 7)
    Author: AFL-CIO News
- ILPA (International Labor Press Association), Publication (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1980; Publication (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Deadline for ILPA Journalistic Awards contest for publications issued in calendar 1979, Publication (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Effects of elimination of budget request for P.L. 93-328, the extended phase in of postage rate increases, in the Reagan F.Y. 1982 budget, Publication (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: ILPA Reporter, 1981; Publication (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: ILPA Reporter - Postfacts, 1981; Publication (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Remarks prepared for delivery by Secretary of Labor Ray Marshal before the Int'l. Labor Press Assoc., 1980; Publication (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Supplement to: ILPA Directory of Member Publications, Publication (Box 220, Folder 8)
- ILPA (International Labor Press Association), Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: correspondence, Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: ILPA Film and Broadcast Competition, 1981; Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: ILPA Film and Broadcast Competition, 1983; Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: ILPA Reporter, 1979; Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: ILPA Reporter, 1981; Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: ILPA Reporter- Postfacts, 1978-1981 (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: ILPA- Special insert for ILPA Reporter, 1981; Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: News and Views from the Senior Citizens, 1980; Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: News and Views from the Senior Citizens, 1984; Publication (Box 220, Folder 9)
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 4th Anniv. Year Book, 1934; Publication (Box 221, Folder 1)
    Author: International Workers Order
  - Item 2: Report to Medical Conference, New York City Central Committee, International Workers Order, 1940; Publication (Box 221, Folder 1)
    Author: Dave Greene
- Miscellaneous correspondence, Publication (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous correspondence and notes, Publication (Box 221, Folder 2)
- Josephine Piccolo, Publication (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Make new friends, the Fraternal Way, Publication (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: My fight with bilbo, 1945; Publication (Box 221, Folder 3)
    Author: Josephine Piccolo
  - Item 3: The Garibaldi, Publication (Box 221, Folder 3)
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Declaration of Policy, Publication (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: IWO Digest for Education Directors, 1941; Publication (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Manual for Lodge Officers of the International Workers Order, 1939; Publication (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Membership book, Publication (Box 221, Folder 4)
    Notes: Empty
  - Item 5: Social games for lodges, 1939; Publication (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Stop wage cuts through taxation!, Publication (Box 221, Folder 4)
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: In Order, 1941; Publication (Box 221, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 3
  - Item 2: In Order, 1942; Publication (Box 221, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 1-2, 5, 7, 9
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Emma Lazarus, 1947; Publication (Box 221, Folder 6)
    Author: Emma Lazarus
  - Item 2: Jewish holidays: their origin and development, 1948; Publication (Box 221, Folder 6)
    Author: Abraham Bick
  - Item 3: Minutes of the 7th National Convention, 1947; Publication (Box 221, Folder 6)
    Author: Jewish People's Fraternal Order
  - Item 4: Speakers Guide No. 1 & 2 - Anti-Semitism in the USA; Palestine and Zionism, Publication (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: The American Jewish Conference, 1943; Publication (Box 221, Folder 6)
    Author: Rubin Saltzman
  - Item 6: Three years, 1944-1947, Publication (Box 221, Folder 6)
    Author: International Workers Order.
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Education for victory, Series 3, IWO, 1942; Publication (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: This is treason!, 1943; Publication (Box 221, Folder 7)
    Author: Sol Vail
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Education for victory, Series 1, 1942; Publication (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Labor and the International Workers Order, 1938; Publication (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Manual for Educational Directors, Publication (Box 221, Folder 8)
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 221, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Alfred Bohlinger vs. International Workers Order, 1951; Publication (Box 221, Folder 9)
    Author: International Workers Order; Alfred Bohlinger
    Notes: Court transcript. Part 1
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Alfred Bohlinger vs. International Workers Order, 1951; Publication (Box 221, Folder 10)
    Notes: Court transcript. Part 2
- United States. Court of Appeals (District of Columbia Circuit), Publication (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Joint appendix, 1953; Publication (Box 222, Folder 1)
    Author: United States. Court of Appeals (District of Columbia Circuit)
- Boleslaw Gebert, Publication (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Poland, 1945; Publication (Box 222, Folder 2)
    Author: Boleslaw Gebert
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 1949 report, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: 7th Convention report, 1947; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
    Author: Peter Shipka
  - Item 3: 7th Convention report, 1947; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
    Author: Sam Milgrom
  - Item 4: A course of 10 lectures on Negro's fight for freedom - two man epochs of American history, 1946; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Add IWO protection to your union protection, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Century of the common man, 1943; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
    Author: Henry A. Wallace
    Notes: two speeches by Henry A. Wallace
  - Item 7: Complete equality: democracy and the Negroes, 1945; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
    Author: Max Bedacht
  - Item 8: Fifteenth Anniv. Almanac - Lincoln Steffens Lodge 500, International Workers Order (1931-1946), Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: GIVE them aid and comfort, Solidarity gifts for soldiers battling Hitlerism, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
    Notes: Coupon booklet
  - Item 10: IWO on parade - 4th Convention, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Labor fraternalism: the fraternal principles and program of the I.W.O., 1941; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Manual for builders, 1939; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Manual for builders, 1949; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Our plan for plenty, 1945; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Outline on Trade Unionism theory and practice, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Public - No. 271 - 74th Congress -- Title 1-Grants to states for old-age assistance, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Report of the General Secretary to the sixth Nat'l Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: The People have never abandoned FDR's policies, 1947; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
    Notes: Second anniversary memorial campaign
  - Item 19: The People vs. Attorney General Tom Clark, before the Court of Public Opinion, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: The unity and merger of the Finnish Workers Federation with the IWO, 1941; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Third Convention of the IWO, report of Comrade Max Bedacht for the Natl. Exec. Comm., Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Trade Unions, Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
    Author: Frederick Engels
    Notes: Three short articles by Engels which originally appeared in the Labour Standard, 1881
  - Item 23: Unity of the Workers Fraternal Movement, 1936; Publication (Box 222, Folder 3)
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Fraternal Outlook - The Teheran Declaration, 1944; Publication (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Report to the General Council of the IWO, 1947; Publication (Box 222, Folder 4)
    Author: Milgrom, Sam
  - Item 3: Report to the Michigan State Convention, International Workers Order, 1940; Publication (Box 222, Folder 4)
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Fifteenth anniversary almanac, 1930-1945, Publication (Box 222, Folder 5)
    Author: International Workers Order. New York City Central Committee.
  - Item 2: For a victory war congress to crush fascism: an open letter to election candidates, Publication (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Journal, Founding conference of the New National IWO Society, 1950; Publication (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Life in the open: an outdoor manual, Publication (Box 222, Folder 5)
    Notes: Booklet from the Educational - Activities Dept
  - Item 5: Report of the General Secretary to the General Exec. Bd., 1941; Publication (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: We gave aid and comfort, report on income disbursements activities response, 1942; Publication (Box 222, Folder 5)
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Introducing the du sable lodge 751, 1946; Publication (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Report, the General Secretary to the sixth national convention., 1944; Publication (Box 222, Folder 6)
- Centro Benefico Juridico de Trabajadores de Cuba, Publication (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1945; Publication (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: De los trabajadores y para los trabajadores, Publication (Box 222, Folder 7)
    Author: Centro Benefico Juridico de Trabajadores de Cuba
  - Item 3: Program and call conference on Puerto Rico's right to freedom, 1946; Publication (Box 222, Folder 7)